<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Resume on NateGB Digital Resume</title>
    <link>https://nategb.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Resume on NateGB Digital Resume</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://nategb.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Gerard-Bowen</title>
      <link>https://nategb.com/homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 16:11:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nategb.com/homepage/</guid>
      <description>A Digital Resume and Personal Homepage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://nategb.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 16:12:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nategb.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my digital resume! My name is Nathan Gerard-Bowen, and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share with you my skills, experience, and passion for Information Technology through this platform.&#xA;I am an Information Technology Specialist, with 3 years of experience in IT. Throughout my career, I have developed a deep understanding of Systems and Network Administration, and have honed my ability to quickly and efficiently find and resolve network and systems issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://nategb.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 16:11:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nategb.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>Nathan Gerard-Bowen nathan@nategb.com | Murfreesboro, TN | https://www.linkedin.com/in/nathan-gb/&#xA;Professional Profile CompTIA-certified IT Operations and Secure Infrastructure Specialist with 3 years of experience in a hybrid-cloud environment. Skilled in efficient troubleshooting and effective communication. Consistently commended for creative problem solving and a willingness to go above and beyond.&#xA;Professional Experience Enterprise Support Technician II | SmileDirectClub | Antioch, TN (October 2023 - December 2023)&#xA;Cultivated strong working relationships between different departments Became a Subject Matter Expert on specialized proprietary software within 2 months of being trained Led a technical training for a team of 30 people located locally and internationally Assisted in migrating manufacturing metric display boards from Windows-based compute sticks to Linux-based Raspberry Pi&amp;rsquo;s Triaged tickets and tracked assets utilizing ServiceNow IT Specialist @ Rutherford County Library System | Smyrna, TN (July 2021 - October 2023)</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
